Guide to the Mab Segrest Papers, 1889-2014 RL.01164
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research and Subject Files, 1918-2005; 10 boxes
  - Printed Materials, 1918-2005
    - Kriegie, by Kenneth W. Simmons, 1960 (Box 108)
    - Vagina Warriors, by Eve Ensler & Joyce Tenneson, 2005 (Box 108)
    - Congressional record, 1966-1971 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Strategies for working, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Extra Magazine, 1994-1996 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Searchlight, 1994-1995 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Intelligence report, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Rutgers University Press, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - The Tuskegee News, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Court documents, undated (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Various writings, undated (Box 110, Folder 1, 2)
    - Honors essay by UNC student, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Reprints considered unsolicited, 1987-1989 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Reprints considered, 1987-1990 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Dannia Southerland paper, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters/Japan, 1992-1995 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Newsweek, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Newspapers and magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Princess Diana, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Media Law handbook, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Statesville doc, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Various publications, undated (Box 111, Folder 7, 8)
    - Brightleaf: A Southern Review of Books, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Delineator ads, 1918 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - 48 Months of Foreign Aggression, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - March announcement, undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Assorted book covers, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - The Terminal Man, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Daisy Miller, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Popi, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Creature from Black Lake, undated (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Hansel and Gretel, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Thumbelina, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Olly Olly Oxen Free, undated (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - US News & World Report, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Trans show, undated (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Articles, 1989-2000
    - Women & multinationals, undated (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Doris Davenport, undated (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Braden, undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Biography of a Chairman Mao Badge, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Media mergers, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - The Traffic in Women…, by Gayle Rubin, [1975] (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Georgia paramilitary action interview, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Robert Jackson: Wilmington trial, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - WPP: Missouri indictment, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Ladyslipper Catalog and Resource Guide, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Affadavit: Holland, undated (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Blue Mountain material, undated (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Bowers v. Hardwick, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Domestic violence, undated (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Essays in Florida History, Florida Endowment for the Humanities, undated (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Expose: The Journal of Interdisciplinary Inquiry, 2006 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Harold Covington, undated (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Kenny Marlow material, undated (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - The March Upcountry, undated (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Paramilitary, undated (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Pornography, undated (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Private school, undated (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Samuel Younge, Jr. in "Free at Last", undated (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Sodomy, undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - South African Constitution, 1994-1996 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Southern Men's Literature, undated (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Various Articles, undated (Box 140, Folder 6, 7)
    - War in Iraq, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 8, 9, Box 141, Folder 1)
    - White Patriot Party trial, undated (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Testing the Limits transcripts, [1988-1994]
    - Tape Transcript: Peg and Jennie Rivera, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Transcript: Alan Sack, [1991] (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Transcript: Armistead Maupin, undated (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Transcript: Brian Freeman, [1990] (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Transcript: Carol/James/Paul Goshorn & Father Jim Gallouzo, [1992] (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Transcript: Donna Minkowitz, [1993] (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Transcript: Gerri Wells, undated (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Transcript: Jack Vincent, [1994] (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Transcript: Jewelle Gomez, undated (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Transcript: John Frohnmayer, [1994] (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Transcript: Karl Knapper, undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Transcript: Kevin Berrill, undated (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Transcript: Robert Vasquez, undated (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Transcript: Tom DiMaria, undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Transcript: Tommy, [1992] (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Various interviews & articles & drafts, undated (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Photographs and Audiovisual Materials, 1929-2004; 6 boxes
  This series contains VHS tapes, cassette tapes, photos, art, and other visual materials related to Dr. Segrest's work, personal life, and research.
  - Visual Materials, 1929-2004
    - Faulkner photographs and High School photographs, 1929-1946, 1966 and undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Family photographs, 1960-1978 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - European travel photos, 1971 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - University Drive photos by Lee Mosley, 1978-1980 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Hurdle Mills, Living in a House photographs, undated (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Mab in floppy hat photo, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Womonwrites photos, including Dorothy Allison, ca. 1980s (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, 1987-1995 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Family Christmas photos, ca. 1990s (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Publicity photos of Mab, ca. 2001 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, 1978-1995 and undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Painting and sketches, undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - 1970s Durham trip to Disneyland, circa 1970s (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Sketches & water colors, circa 1970s (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Beach photos - Topsail, circa 1980s (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Robert Girard Portrait of family, permission to use photo, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - China trip, undated (Box 118, Folder 5, 6)
    - Feminary transparency, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous photos, undated (Box 118, Folder 8, 9)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Mandy Carter/Mab Segrest/Suzanne Pharr birthday sign, undated (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Alligators sign, undated (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Hospital cemetery & angel, undated (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - NOLA before Katrina, New Orleans, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Untitled photograph of a house, undated (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Large photo of Mab, undated (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Her Labia Were Like Flowers & Crossing the DMZ, undated (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Family photographs (CLOSED), undated (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - Takeover: The Trials of Eddie Hatcher, undated (Box 119)
    - The Alabama Experience: Unforgettable Experiences, Tuskegee, Alabama: Living Black and White, undated (Box 119)
    - Honored by the Moon, undated (Box 119)
    - Padares on Sexuality and Sexual Orientation, Tape #3, Harare Assembly, 1998 (Box 119)
    - The Gay Agenda, undated (Box 119)
    - All God's Children, undated (Box 119)
    - Thinking Green: Marta Benavides, undated (Box 119)
    - Mab Segrest partial purple belt test, Annie's 10th Kyu test, Annie's 9th Kyu test, 1994-1996 (Box 119)
    - Network Q: State of the Movement '94, 1994 (Box 119)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Policy Institute, 6th Annual Creating Change, Keynote Speaker Mab Segrest, 1993 (Box 120)
    - When Democracy Works, undated (Box 120)
    - Gay Lives & Culture Wars, undated (Box 120)
    - The Question of Equality: Out Rage '69, 1995 (Box 120)
    - The Question of Equality: Culture Wars, 1995 (Box 120)
    - The Question of Equality: Hollow Liberty, 1995 (Box 120)
    - The Question of Equality: Generation Q, 1995 (Box 120)
    - Raleigh - MNDM Rally, 1988 (Box 120)
    - Sinclair Press Conference/March in Robeson, undated (Box 120)
    - The University of Alabama Center for Public Television, Living Black and White, undated (Box 121)
    - Jennifer Harvey, "What do pickles have to do with my gay rights?", 2002 (Box 121)
    - Happy Birthday Mab!, 1999 (Box 121)
    - Ka Huliau: Mab Segrest Episode #1, 1997 (Box 121)
    - Rough cut of Nix, by K. Bradford, 1996 (Box 121)
    - Connecticut College Presents - Eve Ensler's the Vagina Monologues, 2006 (Box 121)
    - The Tenth Annual Diwali, The Festival of Lights, 2005 (Box 121)
    - Tuskegee, Alabama: Living Black & White, undated (Box 121)